MAHARDHIKA ALIF SURYA

Bogor, Indonesia | <u>+6289637779125</u> | <u>mahardhikaalifsurya@gmail.com</u> | <u>linkedin : Mahardhika Alif Surya</u> | <u>Github :</u> Mahardhikas | Portofolio : Mahardhika Alif Surya

PROFILE

Bachelor degree of Information System with 10 month experience in IT Support and 8 month experience in Front-End Web Development. I am skilled for build a web base ReactJs in a project, the result of the project is a web base application called HealthyCare. Beside that, i am also experienced in managing company database, including design, maintenance and data optimalization. With my experience in Front-End Web Development, I'm interested to continue developing my skills and contribute to creating intuitive and user-friendly applications. I am confident with my technical experience and communication skills, I can make a positive contribution to the company.

EDUCATION

Institut Bisnis dan Informatika Kesatuan

Bachelor of Information System – GPA 3.6/4.0

September 2020 - November 2024

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. Kenlee Indonesia

February 2024 - Present

IT Support SAHL Application

- Manage database with SQL Server.
- Correcting data entry errors made by users through the process of editing and updating the company's database to ensure operational data accuracy.
- Designing and creating new tables to support the development of application features.
- Developing and optimizing stored procedures to accelerate data execution within the system.
- Reporting and documenting technical issues, such as system errors and application performance problems, to the Development team for prompt resolution.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Magang dan Studi Independen Bersertifikat

February 2023 - Juny 2023

Front-End Web Development

- Developed HealthyCare, a web-based application that helps users manage healthy eating habits and balanced nutrition.
- Created user flows to map out the user journey while interacting with the application.
- Designed wireframes and UI designs to ensure an attractive user interface.
- Utilized React.js as the main framework for application development.
- Managed code versioning and project collaboration using Git and GitHub.
- Deployed the application using Netlify, making it accessible across various devices.
- Key features of the web application include BMI calculation, daily article recommendations, and balanced nutrition articles.

SKILLS

Soft Skills

: Skilled and creative, able to work under deadlines, neat, and thorough.

Hard Skills

: Microsoft Office (Word,Excel,Power Point) | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | SQL | ReactJs | Node.js |

MongoDb | Bootstrap | NextJs | MySQL

CERTIFICATION

Sertifikat MSIB BATCH 4 – Front-End Web Development, Kampus Merdeka, 2023 Sertifikat MSIB BATCH 6 – Web Front-End Developer, Kampus Merdeka, 2024 Sertifikat Kompetensi – Data Analyst, Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi, 2024